https://www.masondynamics.com/privacy-policy

Hydraulic Sales and Service - Mason Dynamics, Inc.
0Item
My Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Welcome to Mason Dynamics !
800-653-1382  M-F 8-5:30 EST
Search:
Search
Navigation
ProductsPower UnitsDC Power UnitsAC Power UnitsGas Power UnitsIndustrial Power UnitsAluminum Gear PumpsCylindersQuick CouplingsManifoldsValvesMonoblock ValvesSectional ValvesD03 and D05 ValvesCartridge ValvesHose and FittingsDyna-LiftParts and AccessoriesDC MotorsAC MotorsPumpsMotor Start SwitchesControl BoxesCord AssembliesReservoirsMotor / Pump AdaptorsBattery ChargersSpecialsWarehouse ClearanceServicesAbout UsDownloadsLiterature and GuidesBucher Part DiagramsCylinder PrintsCAD ModelsComplete UnitsPumpsTanksMotors
Contact Us
Blog
Home
Products
Power Units
DC Power Units
AC Power Units
Gas Power Units
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect? We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in any of the following ways: • To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)• To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature• To send periodic emails
How do we protect your information? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies? We do not use cookies.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. Mason Dynamics, Inc.922 W River Center Dr NEComstock Park, MI 49321info@masondynamics.com
Shopping
View Cart
My Account
Order Status
Shop By Brand
Company Information
About Us
Staff
© 2018 Copyright Mason Dynamics. All Rights Reserved.	Magento Themes by parenttechnology.com
Continue Shopping
View cart & checkout
video title
video content
